module.exports = [
{
  question: "What year did the Empire Strikes Back came out?",
  answers: {
    a: "1982",
    b: "1980",
    c: "1977"
  },
  correctAnswer: "1b",
  id: 1
},
{
  question: "What kind of specie is Chewbacca?",
  answers: {
    a: "Trandoshian",
    b: "Droid",
    c: "Wookie"
  },
  correctAnswer: "2c",
  id: 2
},
{
  question: "Which model is Millenium Falcon?",
  answers: {
    a: "BTL Y-Wing",
    b: "YT-1300 Light Freighter",
    c: "Executor-Class Star Dreadnought"
  },
  correctAnswer: "3b",
  id: 3
},
{
  question: "Who is Luke's father?",
  answers: {
    a: "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
    b: "Anakin Skywalker",
    c: "R2-D2"
  },
  correctAnswer: "4b",
  id: 4
},
{
  question: "How fast the Millenium Falcon completed the Kessel Run?",
  answers: {
    a: "14 parsecs",
    b: "more than 18 parsecs",
    c: "less then 12 parsecs"
  },
  correctAnswer: "5c",
  id: 5
},
{
  question: "In which movie Anakin Skywalker became a member of the Jedi Council?",
  answers: {
    a: "Episode III The Revenge of The Sith",
    b: "Episode I The Phantom Menace",
    c: "Episode II Attack of the Clones"
  },
  correctAnswer: "6a",
  id: 6
},
{
  question: "How old was Yoda when he died?",
  answers: {
    a: "90 years old",
    b: "700 years old",
    c: "900 years old"
  },
  correctAnswer: "7c",
  id: 7
},
{
  question: "In Return of the Jedi, Battle of Yavin was in year?",
  answers: {
    a: "1922 BBY",
    b: "0 BBY",
    c: "19 ABY"
  },
  correctAnswer: "8b",
  id: 8
},
{
  question: "What was first destroyed by the Death Star?",
  answers: {
    a: "Jedha City",
    b: "planet Alderaan",
    c: "Citadel on Scarif"
  },
  correctAnswer: "9a",
  id: 9
},
{
  question: "In which Star Wars movie C-3PO had a red arm?",
  answers: {
    a: "Episode IV A New Hope",
    b: "Episode I The Phantom Menace",
    c: "Episode VII The Force Awakens"
  },
  correctAnswer: "10c",
  id: 10
}
];
